[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "name": "1",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "At a party do you:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Interact with many, including strangers",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Interact with a few, known to you",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "name": "2",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Realistic than speculative",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Speculative than realistic",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "name": "3",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Is it worse to:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Have your “head in the clouds”",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Be “in a rut”",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "name": "4",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more impressed by:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Principles",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Emotions",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "name": "5",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are more drawn toward the:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Convincing",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Touching",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "name": "6",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you prefer to work:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "To deadlines",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Just “whenever”",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "name": "7",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you tend to choose:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Rather carefully",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Somewhat impulsively",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "name": "8",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "At parties do you:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Stay late, with increasing energy",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Leave early with decreased energy",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "name": "9",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more attracted to:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Sensible people",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Imaginative people",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "name": "10",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more interested in:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "What is actual",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "What is possible",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "name": "11",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In judging others are you more swayed by:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Laws than circumstances",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Circumstances than laws",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "name": "12",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In approaching others is your inclination to be somewhat:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Objective",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Personal",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "name": "13",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Punctual",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Leisurely",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "name": "14",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Does it bother you more having things:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Incomplete",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Completed",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "name": "15",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In your social groups do you:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Keep abreast of other’s happenings",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Get behind on the news",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "name": "16",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In doing ordinary things are you more likely to:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Do it the usual way",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Do it your own way",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "name": "17",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Writers should:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "“Say what they mean and mean what they say”",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Express things more by use of analogy",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "name": "18",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which appeals to you more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Consistency of thought",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Harmonious human relationships",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "name": "19",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more comfortable in making:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Logical judgments",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Value judgments",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "name": "20",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you want things:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Settled and decided",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Unsettled and undecided",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "name": "21",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Would you say you are more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Serious and determined",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Easy-going",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "name": "22",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In phoning do you:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "Rarely question that it will all be said",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Rehearse what you’ll say",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "name": "23",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Facts:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "“Speak for themselves”",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "Illustrate principles",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "name": "24",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are visionaries:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "somewhat annoying",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "rather fascinating",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "name": "25",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more often:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "a cool-headed person",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "a warm-hearted person",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "name": "26",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Is it worse to be:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "unjust",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "merciless",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "name": "27",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Should one usually let events occur:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "by careful selection and choice",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "randomly and by chance",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "name": "28",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you feel better about:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "having purchased",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "having the option to buy",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "name": "29",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In company do you:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "initiate conversation",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "wait to be approached",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "name": "30",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Common sense is:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "rarely questionable",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "frequently questionable",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "name": "31",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Children often do not:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "make themselves useful enough",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "exercise their fantasy enough",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "name": "32",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In making decisions do you feel more comfortable with:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "standards",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "feelings",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "name": "33",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "firm than gentle",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "gentle than firm",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "name": "34",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which is more admirable:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "the ability to organize and be methodical",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "the ability to adapt and make do",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "name": "35",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you put more value on:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "infinite",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "open-minded",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "name": "36",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Does new and non-routine interaction with others:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "stimulate and energize you",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "tax your reserves",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "name": "37",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more frequently:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "a practical sort of person",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "a fanciful sort of person",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "name": "38",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more likely to:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "see how others are useful",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "see how others see",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "name": "39",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which is more satisfying:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "to discuss an issue thoroughly",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "to arrive at agreement on an issue",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "name": "40",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which rules you more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "your head",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "your heart",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "name": "41",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more comfortable with work that is:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "contracted",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "done on a casual basis",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "name": "42",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you tend to look for:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "the orderly",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "whatever turns up",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "name": "43",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you prefer:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "many friends with brief contact",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "a few friends with more lengthy contact",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "name": "44",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you go more by:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "facts",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "principles",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "name": "45",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more interested in:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "production and distribution",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "design and research",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "name": "46",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which is more of a compliment:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "“There is a very logical person.” ",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "“There is a very sentimental person.”",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "name": "47",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you value in yourself more that you are:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "unwavering",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "devoted",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "name": "48",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you more often prefer the",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "final and unalterable statement",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "tentative and preliminary statement",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "name": "49",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more comfortable:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "after a decision",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "before a decision",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "name": "50",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "speak easily and at length with strangers",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "find little to say to strangers",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "name": "51",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more likely to trust your:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "experience",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "hunch",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "name": "52",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you feel:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "more practical than ingenious",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "more ingenious than practical",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "name": "53",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which person is more to be complimented – one of:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "clear reason",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "strong feeling",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "name": "54",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you inclined more to be:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "fair-minded",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "sympathetic",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "name": "55",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Is it preferable mostly to:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "make sure things are arranged",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "just let things happen",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "name": "56",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In relationships should most things be:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "re-negotiable",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "random and circumstantial",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "name": "57",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "When the phone rings do you:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "hasten to get to it first",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "hope someone else will answer",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "name": "58",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you prize more in yourself:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "a strong sense of reality",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "a vivid imagination",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "name": "59",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you drawn more to:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "fundamentals",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "overtones",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "name": "60",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which seems the greater error:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "to be too passionate",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "to be too objective",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "name": "61",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you see yourself as basically:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "hard-headed",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "soft-hearted",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "name": "62",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which situation appeals to you more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "the structured and scheduled",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "the unstructured and unscheduled",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "name": "63",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you a person that is more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "routinized than whimsical",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "whimsical than routinized",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "name": "64",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Are you more inclined to be:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "easy to approach",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "somewhat reserved",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "name": "65",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "In writings do you prefer:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "the more literal",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "the more figurative",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "name": "66",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Is it harder for you to:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "identify with others",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "utilize others",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "name": "67",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which do you wish more for yourself:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "clarity of reason",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "strength of compassion",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "name": "68",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Which is the greater fault:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "being indiscriminate",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "being critical",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "name": "69",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you prefer the:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "planned event",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "unplanned event",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "name": "70",
        "mode": "Single",
        "question": "Do you tend to be more:",
        "options": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "name": "1",
                "answer": "deliberate than spontaneous",
                "value": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "name": "2",
                "answer": "spontaneous than deliberate",
                "value": 2
            },
        ]
    },
]
